한가지 배웠어, 치즈야
We learned one thing, Cheese:
치어리더와 고성능 폭약은
서로 어울리지 않는다는 거지
Cheerleaders and high explosives
don't mix.
나도 동의해, 맥
You can say that again, Mac.
나 혼자선 못했을 거야
넌 천재야
I couldn't have done it alone.
You're a genius.
그래? 그럼 왜 내 비디오는
계속 12:00를 깜빡거리는 거지?
Oh, yeah? Well, how come I can't get
my VCR to stop blinking 12:00?
What did you guys think?
그래서 어떻게들 생각해?
-Hey, the phone.
-I got it. I got it.
- 아, 전화다
- 내가 받을께, 내가 받을께
Hold on. It's your mom.
잠깐만요
조이, 네 엄마다
-It's Mommy.
-That's nice.
- 엄마래
- 좋겠네
Ma, so what did you think?
엄마, 그래서 어땠어요?
Well...
글쎄...
that was okay.
괜찮았는데
It wasn't the best.
최고는 아니었지
That was one
of the worst things ever...
내가 본 것 중
최악이다
and not just on TV.
TV에서 본 것만
얘기하는 게 아냐
-What should we say?
-The lighting was okay.
- 뭐라고 해주지?
- 조명은 괜찮았어
You got lighting last time.
Lighting is mine.
넌 저번에 조명 말했어
이번엔 내 거야
I have costumes.
의상은 내 거
That means I'm stuck with:
그럼, 난 이 말밖에 없잖아
'방금 TV 속에 있는 널 봤는데
넌 여기 앉아 있잖아, 와!'
"So we were watching you in there, and
you were sitting right here. Whoa."
-What about you?
-I don't know.
- 피비, 너는?
- 몰라
I can't lie to him again.
Oh, no, I.. No.
다시 거짓말 할 수 없어
아니, 그래
I'm just gonna press
my breasts up against him.
그냥 내 가슴을
걔한테 밀어붙일 거야
-And say nothing?
-Yeah, that's right.
- 아무 말도 안하고?
- 응, 맞아
Wow, my folks really liked it.
우리 부모님은
아주 맘에 들었다셔
What did you guys think?
너흰 어떻게 생각해?
It wasn't that good.
그렇게 좋지는 않았는데
The One With Rachel's Assistant
자기가 좋아하는 동물이 자신에
대해 뭔가 말해준다고 생각해?
Do you think that your favorite animal
says much about you?
내 등 뒤에서 말야?
You mean behind my back?
오늘 무슨 일이 있었게?
말해도 못 믿을 걸
You'll never believe
what happened to me today.
- 사무실에 앉아 있는데...
- 얘들아!
-I am sitting in my office..
-You guys!
내 에이전트가 뭐라고 했게?
Guess what my agent just said?
조이, 나 지금
말하는 중이었어
-I'm in the middle of a story here.
-Sorry, you finish.
미안, 먼저 끝내
사무실에 앉아있는데
누가 들어왔게?
I'm sitting in my office,
and guess who walks in.
나 TV 쇼
두 편에 출연한다
I'm gonna be on two TV shows.
잘됐구나
That's great.
- 조이
- 얘기 안 끝났어?
-Joey.
-You weren't finished?
'사무실에 누가 들어왔게'가
내 얘기의 끝이었어
Yeah, "Guess who walks
into my office" is my story.
랄프 로렌이
사무실에 걸어 들어왔어
Ralph Lauren walked into my office.
얘기 새로 시작할 거면
내 얘기라도 끝내게 해줘라
If you're starting another story,
at least let me finish mine.
같은 얘기야
It's the same story.
와, 진짜 길다
Wow, it's really long.
랄프가 내 일에
아주 만족했다면서
Ralph just came in to tell me
that he's so happy with my work...
폴로 소매업의
상품화 부장으로 승진시킨대
that he wants me to be the new
merchandising manager for Polo retail.
- 웨딩드레스는 계속 할인 받지?
- 응
Still get a discount on wedding gowns?
너무 잘됐다, 얘
I'm so happy for you.
이건 정말
우리 생의 나날들이구나
These really are
the "days of our lives."
- 뭐라고?
- 물어보니까 얘기해주지
-What?
-Well, since you ask...
생의 나날들에
다시 출연하게 됐어
They want me back on
Days of Our Lives.
난 월급도 많이 올랐어!
I get a big pay raise!
어머나!
Oh, hey!
난 드레이크 라모레의
쌍둥이 형 스트라이커 역을 맡았어
I'll be playing Drake Ramoray's
twin brother, Stryker.
난 내 개인 조수도
고용하게 된다
I get to hire my own assistant.
난 너무 빨리 일어섰더니
머리가 띵하다
I got a head rush
from standing up too fast.
이 직장에서는
4년간 일했다고요?
You were at this job four years?
- 그래요
- 아주 훌륭한 이력이네요, 힐다
-That's right.
-This is all very impressive, Hilda.
마지막 질문이 하나 있어요
I just have one last question for you.
나 어땠죠? 잘했나요?
How did I do? Was this okay?
- 네?
- 나 면담자는 처음 해 봐요
-What?
-I've never interviewed anyone.
내 밑에
사람을 둬 본 적이 없죠
I've never had anyone work for me.
어렸을 때 가정부는 있었지만
이거랑은 틀리죠
When I was a kid we had a maid,
but this isn't the same.
그렇죠, 아주 틀리죠
No, dear, it's not.
그건 나도 알지만요
And I know that.
어쨌든, 방문해줘서 고마워요
Well, thank you so much for coming in.
- 만나서 반갑구요
- 반가웠어요
-Nice to meet you.
-Good meeting you.
그래요
All right.
나 완전 프로잖아
I'm a total pro.
- 안녕하세요
- 우와
-Hello.
-Wow.
안녕하세요, 모델들은
복도 끝으로 가세요
Hi, yes, I'm sorry.
The models are down the hall.
전 조수직 때문에 왔는데요
I'm here about the assistant job.
정말요?
Really?
그래요, 그럼, 자
거기 앉으세요
Okay, well, then, all right.
Well, just have a seat there.
성함이 어떻게 되죠?
So what's your name?
태그 존스요
Tag Jones.
응, 계속해봐요
Uh-huh, go on.
그거예요, 그게 제 이름 전부죠
That's it. That's my whole name.
그게 이름 전부라고요?
그렇죠
That's your whole name.
Of course.
자, 여기 한 번 봅시다
Okay, let's just have a look-see here.
사무실에서 일해본 적이 없고
경험은 별로 없지만...
I haven't worked in an office before.
I don't have much experience..
무슨 소리예요? 3년동안
페인트 칠한 경험도 있고
What are you talking about?
You got three years painting houses...
두 여름 내내
TGl 프라이데이에서 일했네요
two whole summers
at TGl Friday's.
자격미달이죠, 알아요
It's lame, I know.
하지만 전 목표지향적이고
열심히 배울 의향이 있고...
But I'm a goal-oriented person,
eager to learn..
잠깐만요
Just hold on a second, please.
이건 인사과를 위한 거예요, 모두가
다 해야 되죠, 좀 일어서 볼래요?
It's for human resources. Everybody
has to. Would you stand up?
아니, 안 돼요
No, no, no.
야
Hey.
- 어쨌든, 나 가봐야겠다
- 그래, 안녕
-Anyway, I should go.
-Okay. Bye.
- 안녕, 자기야
- 자기, 안녕
-Hey, sweetie.
-Hi, sweetie.
뭘 그렇게 속닥거렸어?
What was with all the whispering?
말 못해, 비밀이야
I can't tell you. It's a secret.
비밀? 결혼한 사람들은
비밀 갖고 있으면 안되지
Secret? Married people aren't
supposed to have secrets.
우린 서로 너무
사랑하고 존경하잖아
We love and respect
one another too much.
그래도 안 돼
But still, no.
우린 서로에게 다 얘기해야 돼
난 네가 모르는 비밀은 없는데
We should tell each other everything.
I don't have secrets from you.
그럼, 고2때 디즈니랜드에서
로스한테 일어났던 일이 뭐야?
Really? So tell me what happened
to Ross, junior year at Disneyland.
아니, 그건 안 돼
No, I can't do that.
대신 피비가 한 얘기를 해줄께
I'll tell you what Phoebe said.
- 그래
-Okay.
로스하고
디즈니랜드에 갔거든
So Ross and I
are going to Disneyland.
타코를 먹으려고 식당에 들렀지
We stop at this restaurant for tacos.
그 식당이란 게, 사람 하나에다
차 트렁크에 숯불 화로 하나야
When I say restaurant, I mean a guy,
a hibachi, and the trunk of his car.
그래서 로스가
타코를 한 10개 먹고
So Ross has about ten tacos.
스페이스 마운틴을 탔는데
로스가 기분이 좀 이상하대잖아
Anyway, we're on Space Mountain
and Ross starts to feel a little iffy.
세상에, 토했구나
Oh, my God. He threw up?
토하는 것보다는
좀 남쪽 동네였어
No, he visited a town
a little south of throw up.
- 진짜야?
- 그래
피비의 비밀은 뭔데?
What was Phoebe's secret?
피비의 옛날 안마소에 있던
낸시 톰슨이 해고된대
Nancy Thompson, from Phoebe's
old massage place, is getting fired.
그거야? 내 디즈니랜드 얘기를
그거랑 바꿨단 말야?
That's it? I gave up my
Disneyland story for that?
그랬지롱
네가 졌어, 바보야!
That's right. You lose, sucker!
그래도 제발
나랑 결혼해 줘
Please still marry me.
챈들러, 너 조수 두고 있지?
You have an assistant, right?
전화왔었어?
Did she call?
내가 아프다고 했지?
언제나 내가 아프다고 해야 돼
You told her I was sick, right?
Always tell her I am sick.
그냥, 난 모르겠어
누굴 고용해야 할 지
I don't know.
How do you decide who to hire?
둘 중에서 골라야 되는데
I have it down to two people.
한 명은 추천서도 대단하고
경력도 아주 많아
One has great references
and a lot of experience.
- 그 다음에 한 남자가 있는데...
- 그 사람은?
-And then, there's this guy.
-What about him?
그를 사랑해
I love him.
너무 멋져서
울고 싶을 정도야
He's so pretty, I want to cry.
어쩔 줄을 모르겠어
I don't know what to do.
어떻게 해야 할 지는 알잖아
첫 번째 사람을 고용해야지
Come on, you know what to do.
You hire the first one.
잘 생긴 걸로 조수를 고용하면
안되지, 경력을 보고 해야지
Don't hire assistants because they're
cute. Do it because they're qualified.
응
Uh-huh.
무슨 말인지 알아, 이치에 맞지
근데, 한 가지만 더 얘기할께
I hear you. You make a lot of sense.
Can I just say one more thing?
얼마나 멋진지 봐
Look how pretty.
어디 보자
Let me see.
어머나, 세상에
Oh, my God.
근데, 안 돼
Oh. But, no.
안 돼, 이 사람을 고용하면
직업정신에 어긋나
No. You can't hire him
because it's not professional.
이거 내 거지, 응?
This is for me, yes?
알았어, 네가 맞아
내일 힐다를 고용할께
Okay, you're right.
I'll hire Hilda tomorrow.
바보 같은 일자리에
안성맞춤인, 늙은 힐다
Dumb, old, perfect-for-the-job Hilda.
어디 보여줘봐
Let me see.
우와!
Wow!
이거 모니카 보여주지 마
Don't show this to Monica.
그리고 내가 '우와'한 것도
말하지 마
And don't tell her about the "Wow!"
'생의 나날들'
- 어, 조이
- 안녕하세요, 테리
-Hey, Joey.
-Hey, Terry.
- 반갑군, 그래
- 오랜만이에요
-Nice to see you again.
-Been a while.
이상하죠, 복도들이
전보다 좁아보이는데요
Funny, these halls look smaller
than they used to.
다른 빌딩이잖아
It's a different building.
그래서...
So...
스트라이커 라모레
역이라고요?
Stryker Ramoray, huh?
- 언제 시작하죠?
- 지금 하지 뭐
-When do I start?
-How about right now?
그래요
Okay.
여기 오디션 장면들이야
Here are the audition scenes.
오디션요? 저한테 배역을
주는 걸로 알았는데요
I thought you
were offering me the part.
왜 그런 생각을?
Why?
제가 스트라이커의 쌍둥이 동생
드레이크 라모레 역이었잖아요
I was Doctor Drake Ramoray,
Stryker's twin brother.
나보다 나를 더 닮은
사람이 있나요?
Who looks more like me than me, right?
누구든 오디션은 해야지
Everybody has to audition.
있죠, 테리, 사실
난 이걸 할 필요는 없어요
You know, Terry,
I don't really need to do this.
이제 저만의
케이블 TV 시리즈도 있다구요
I got my own cable TV series...
로보트까지 등장해요
with a robot.
미안, 조이
이건 어쩔 수가 없네
I'm sorry, Joey.
That's the way it is.
그렇다면...
Well...
당신이 꽤 특별하다고
생각하시나 보죠?
I guess you think
you're pretty special.
여기 호사스런 복도 좁은
빌딩 안에 앉아서
Sitting up here in your fancy,
small-halled building...
스타들더러
이래라 저래라 하면서 말예요
making stars jump
through hoops for you.
근데, 있잖아요
Well, you know what?
이 한 스타는 이래라 못...
This is one star whose hoop..
이 스타는 이래저...
이래라 못...
This is the star the hoop..
This hoop..
난 드레이크 라모레였다고요!
I was Doctor Drake Ramoray!
안녕, 태그
여기 웬일이죠?
Hi, Tag. What are you doing here?
어제 절 깔보지 않으셔서
감사하단 말을 하고 싶었어요
I came to thank you for not laughing
in my face yesterday.
화분이 하나도 없는 것 같아서
하나 갖고...
I noticed there were no plants
so I brought you your first.
사무실에 화분이 있군요
There is a plant in your office.
그런 것 같죠
Kind of.
Right.
이력서에다 '관찰력이
우수하다'라고는 못 쓰겠네요
So I guess I shouldn't put
"good at noticing stuff" on my resume.
- 고마워요
- 어쨌든...
-Thank you.
-Anyway...
누군가 이미 고용하셨겠죠?
I'm guessing you hired somebody.
글쎄...
Well...
알겠어요
Gotcha.
만나주셔서
다시 한 번 감사해요
Thanks again for meeting with me.
근데, 그 쪽을 고용했는데
But I hired you.
- 네?
- 당신이 고용됐어요
-What?
-Yeah, you got the job.
- 제 새 조수가 됐어요
- 제가요?
-You're my new assistant.
-I am?
그래요
Yeah.
- 믿어지지가 않아요
- 나도
-I can't believe it.
-Me either.
먼저 해야 할 일은
아래층에 내려가서
First, I need you to go downstairs...
find a woman named Hilda,
and tell her to go home.
힐다라는 여자를 찾아서
집에 가라고 해줘요
- 안녕
- 안녕, 왔어? 잘 됐다
-Hey.
-Hey, good you're home.
'제길, 또 너냐'라는 말보단
듣기 좋구먼
Always nicer to hear than,
"Oh, crap, you again."
자기, 자기 위해서 뭘 만들었다
Hey, sweetie, I made you a surprise.
- 그래?
- 그래, 타코
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah, tacos.
자기 얘기를 들은 후로
너무 먹고 싶었어
Ever since that story,
I've had such a craving.
얘기의 핵심을
이해 못했나보지?
Did you not understand the story?
- 안녕
- 안녕, 별일 없냐?
-Hey.
-Hey, what's up?
그냥 저녁을 뭘 먹을까
생각 중이었어
Nothing. Just figuring out
what to do for dinner.
이건 뭐야? 저녁거리?
저녁 만들고 있었어?
Hey, what's that? Dinner stuff?
You making dinner?
아니
No.
그건 뭐야? 타코?
What's over there? Tacos?
아니, 아니
No. No.
그냥...
쇠고기 빙그레 만두지
They're just ground beef smileys.
어...그건 타코잖아
Those are tacos.
미안합니다, 미스터 멕시코
Excuse me, Mr. Mexico.
어쨌든, 난 안 먹을래
아직도 그건 못 먹겠어
Either way, I'll pass.
Still can't eat those.
뭐가 그렇게 웃겨?
What's so funny?
웃지 않았는데
I'm not laughing.
너 말했구나!
You told her!
낸시 톰슨이 해고된대
Nancy Thompson's getting fired.
야, 그건 식중독이었어
내가 뭐 원해서 그랬나!
Okay, okay. I had food poisoning.
It's not like I chose to do it!
'어떻게 하면 이 공원놀이가
더 재미있을까'라고 했을까봐?
It's not like I said,
"What would make this ride more fun?"
맞아, 맞아, 미안
웃으면 안되는 건데
Right. You're right, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be laughing.
오빠를 위해서
신문지를 깔아야겠지
I should be
laying down papers for you.
- 어떻게 그럴수 있어?
- 그래야 했어, 우린 결혼하잖아
-How could you?
-I had to. We're getting married.
부부끼리 비밀이 있어선 안 돼
Married couples can't keep secrets.
그럼 모니카가 애틀랜틱 시티의
일을 알아야 하겠네
I guess Monica should know
about Atlantic City.
야아!
Dude!
- 무슨 일이 있었는데?
- 챈들러랑 나랑 바에 갔는데
-What happened?
-Chandler and I are in a bar...
지금 내가 '야아'
하는 소리 못들었냐?
Did you not hear me say, "Dude"?
어떤 여자가 챈들러한테
눈길을 보내잖아
and this girl
is making eyes at Chandler.
그래서 챈들러가 그녀한테 갔지
보니까 둘이 키스하고 있잖아
So he goes over to her and, after
a minute or two, I see them kissing.
'바에서 여자랑 놀아나는
남자가 아닌데'라고 생각하겠지
You're thinking he's not the type
to go to bars and make out with girls.
그래, 맞아
그런 남자가 아냐
And you're right.
He's not the type...
바에 가서 '여자'랑
놀아나는 남자가 아니지
to go to bars
and makes out with girls.
남자랑 키스했구나?!
You kissed a guy?
세상에!
Oh, my God!
내 자신을 변호하자면, 거긴 어두웠고
그는 아주 예쁜 남자였어
In my defense, it was dark
and he was a very pretty guy.
모니카, 난 너무 웃어서...
Oh, Mon, I laughed so hard..
너무 세게 웃어서 또 속옷을
내버렸어야 했다구?
So hard we had to throw out
your underwear again?
뭐라 해도 좋아, 임마
넌 남자랑 키스했어
Whatever, dude. You kissed a guy.
-Hi.
-Hey.
- 안녕
힐다는 어때? 잘 돼가?
How's Hilda working out?
오, 내 새 조수
잘 하고 있지
Oh, my new assistant
is working out. Yes.
그 여자
취직 돼서 기뻐하냐?
She happy she got the job?
내 새 조수는 내가 새 조수를
고용한 사실을 아주 기뻐하지
My new assistant is very happy
that I hired my new assistant.
여보세요
Hello.
네, 잠깐만 기다려주세요
Oh, hey! Can you hang on a second?
맥 앤드 치즈의 프로듀서들이야
잠깐만 실례하겠수다
It's the producers at Mac and Cheese,
if you'll excuse me for a minute.
전화 잘하셨네요, 마침
내주 대본을 읽고 있던 참이에요
Hey, funny you should call. I was
just looking over next week's script.
취소됐다구요!
Canceled!
그러니까, 방영을
안한다는 뜻인가요?
Like, they're taking it off the air?
알았어요, 월요일에 보죠
All right, I'll see you Monday.
더 이상 찍지도 않는다구요?
We're not even shooting them anymore?
알았어요, 안녕히 계세요
All right. Bye.
맥 앤드 치즈가 취소됐어!
They canceled Mac and Cheese!
- 저런
- 안됐구나, 조이
-Sorry.
-Sorry, Joey.
왜 그랬을까?
꽤 좋은 쇼였는데, 안 그래?
Why would they do that?
It was a good show, right?
비밀 얘기하고 싶어?
좋아, 대학교 때
You want to tell secrets?
Okay, in college...
로스는 쫄쫄이
다리토시를 신고 다녔어
Ross used to wear leg warmers.
그래? 챈들러는 '바닐라 아이스
닮기 대회'에 참가해서 이겼다
All right, Chandler entered a Vanilla
Ice look-alike contest and won.
로스는 4위를 차지하고 울었다!
Ross came in fourth and cried!
오, 웃기니?
그게 웃기다고 생각해?
Oh, is that funny?
You find that funny?
챈들러도 네 비밀을 좀
아는 게 좋겠다
Maybe Chandler should know
your secrets too.
난 이미 다 얘기했어
조용해!
I already told him everything.
You shush!
모니카가 벌로
굶고 방으로 보내졌는데
Once, she was sent to bed
without dinner...
자기가 만든 보석함에 붙은
마카로니를 떼어먹었지
so she ate the macaroni off
a jewelry box she'd made.
로스는 토요일 밤마다 안나가고
노인쇼 황금기 소녀들을 봤다
Ross stayed home every Saturday night
to watch Golden Girls.
모니카는 13살 때까지
시계를 못 읽었다
Monica couldn't tell time
until she was 13.
어떤 사람들한테는 어려워!
It's hard for some people!
물론이지
Of course it is.
와
Wow.
- 챈들러는 내 속옷 입고 출근했다!
- 야!
-Chandler wore my underwear to work!
-Hey!
미안, 로스에 대한 게
더 이상 생각이 안나서
I'm sorry, I couldn't think
of any more for Ross.
대학교 때 챈들러는 취해서
In college, Chandler got drunk...
기숙사 청소하는 아줌마랑 잤어
and slept with the lady
who cleaned our dorm.
그건 너였잖아
That was you.
어쨌건, 임마
넌 남자랑 키스했잖아
Whatever, dude. You kissed a guy.
어떻게 나한테
이런 일이 있을 수 있지?
How could this happen to me?
어제는 TV 쇼가 둘이었는데
오늘은...한 개도 없어
Yesterday, I had two TV shows.
Today, I got nothing.
잠깐, 생의 나날들은
어떻게 됐어?
Wait a minute,
what happened to Days of our Lives?
글쎄, 그 쪽은 나한테
좀 화가 나있을 지도 몰라
Well, they might be a little mad
at me over there.
무슨 일이 있었어?
What happened?
뭐, 내가 좀 기분 상해서
어디로 꺼지라고 했다고나 할까
Well, maybe I got a little upset, and
maybe I told them where they could go.
조이, 대체 왜 그랬어?
Joey, why would you do that?
나더러 오디션하라고 하잖아!
Because! They wanted me to audition.
배우인 너한테? 미쳤다!
You, an actor? That's madness!
레이첼 그린 사무실입니다
Rachel Green's office.
태그
Tag.
안녕, 그건 누구였죠?
Hi, who was that?
아무도 아니에요
그냥 연습하고 있었어요
Nobody. I was just practicing.
정말?
Really?
- 안녕
- 레이첼 그린 사무실입니다
-Hi.
-Hi, Rachel Green's office.
당신이 힐다인가 보죠
You must be Hilda.
이 사람은 태그야, 여긴 피비
피비, 잠깐 나 좀 볼래?
He's Tag. This is Phoebe.
Phoebe, can I see you for a sec?
피비
Phoebe.
- 이름 참 예쁘네요
- 내 이름이 좋아요?
-Great name.
-You like that?
- 전화번호도 한번 들어봐요
- 자, 금방 돌아올께요
-You should hear my phone number.
-Okay.
그래서, 아주 귀여운 걸
하나 고용했군, 응?
So you hired yourself
a little treat, did you?
어떻게 보일 지는 알겠지만
정말이지...
I know how it looks,
but I am telling you..
너 조수랑
사귀는 건 안 돼
You can't get involved
with your assistant.
알아, 이 사람을 고용한 게
똑똑한 짓은 아니었다는 것도
I know that, and I know hiring him was
not the smartest thing I've ever done.
하지만 지금부터는 정말로
공적인 관계만 유지할 거야
But, from now on,
I swear this is strictly professional.
- 네
- 안녕, 레이첼
-Yes.
-Hey, Rachel.
안녕
Hi.
조수 귀엽다
어떤 사람이에요?
Cute assistant. What's his story?
- 혹시...
- 게이냐구? 그래
-Is he..
-Gay? Yeah.
안녕하세요, 테리
Hey, Terry.
조이 트리비아니
Joey Tribbiani.
그 큰 머리가 우리 좁은 복도를
통과했다니 놀랍군
Surprised your big head
could fit through our small halls.
- 나 가봐야 하네, 조이
- 잠깐, 테리! 들어봐요
-I gotta go, Joey.
-Wait, Terry! Look.
전의 일, 정말 미안해요
I'm really sorry about before.
오디션하기엔 너무 잘나간다고
생각한 제가 바보였어요
I was an idiot, thinking I'm too big
to audition for you.
- 한 번만 기회를 더 줘요
- 안 돼
-Give me another chance.
-I can't.
잠깐만요, 테리, 제발!
Wait, Terry, please!
저기, 다른 직장도 잃었어요
Look, I just lost my other job, okay?
이 일이 정말로 필요해요
You have no idea how much I need this.
제발 도와줘요
Please, help me out.
옛 정을 생각해서라도
For old times' sake.
이 사람은 5년째 혼수 상태예요
가망이 없어요
This guy's been in a coma
for five years. It's hopeless.
아니오, 닥터 스트라이커 라모레는
기적을 행하는 사람이에요
It's not. Dr. Stryker Ramoray
is a miracle worker.
여기 오시네
Here he comes.
안녕하세요
Good morning.
드레이크, 네 형 스트라이커야
내 말 들려?
Drake, it's your brother, Stryker.
Can you hear me?
그리고, 컷
And cut.
다시 컴백했다!
I'm back, baby!
내 자신을 변호하자면 말이지
You know, in my defense...
그 마카로니엔 반짝이도 안 붙었고
풀도 아주 조금만 묻었었어
there was no glitter on
the macaroni and very little glue.
내 자신을 변호하자면
청소부 아줌마가 날 꼬신 거였어
And in my defense,
the cleaning lady came on to me.
- 지금도 시계 읽는 게 어렵니?
- 아니
-Do you have trouble telling time now?
-No.
- 얼른, 몇 시야?
- 남자랑 키스할 시간?
-Quick, what time is it?
-Time to kiss a guy?
왜 웃어, 기저귀씨?
What are you laughing at, Pampers?
있잖아, 내가 부부끼리는
You know when I said
married people...
비밀 없이 서로 모든 걸
알아야 한다고 했지?
should share everything
and not have any secrets?
- 응
- 그건 어리석었어, 하지 말자
-Yeah?
-That was stupid. Let's not do that.
백번 동감이야
Absolutely.
우리가 얘기했던 거
딴 사람한테는 얘기 안 하기다
We should keep the stuff we told
each other secret from everyone else.
그럼, 당연하지
Yeah, definitely.
그래, 그럼 난 이제
Okay. If you'll excuse me...
스페이스 마운틴 일을
모르는 사람들과 어울리러 간다
I'm gonna hang out with people who
don't know the Space Mountain story.
- 그럼, 피비는 피하는 게 좋겠다
- 야!
-Then I'd steer clear of Phoebe.
-Man!
그러진 않겠지만, 우리 사무실
사람들하고도 어울리지 마
Not that you would, but I wouldn't
hang out with the guys at my office.
안녕
Hi.
- 시간 있으세요?
- 그래요, 무슨 일인데?
-Do you have a minute?
-Sure. What's up?
오늘 점심 때
데이트 신청을 두 번 받았어요
I got asked out twice today
while I was at lunch...
남자한테서요
by guys.
- 정말이요?
- 네
-Really?
-Yeah.
누구한테 제가
게이라고 했어요?
Did you tell someone that I was gay?
오, 사람들이
알지 않았으면 했나보죠?
Oh, did you not want people
to know that?
전 게이 아니에요, 특히 부장님이
그렇게 생각하는 건 원치 않아요
I'm not gay. I especially wouldn't
want you to think I was gay.
그건 왜죠?
Why is that?
- 말하면 안 될 것 같아요
- 오, 말해도 돼요
-I don't think I should say.
-Oh, you can say.
어서요, 내게 말 못하는 게
있으면 안 되지
Come on, I don't want you to feel
like you can't tell me things.
- 그래요
-Okay.
- 저기...
- 응
-Well...
-Yeah.
피비란 친구분에게
데이트 신청하고 싶어요
I'd love to ask out
your friend Phoebe.
글쎄, 걘 레즈인데
Yeah, she's gay.